[id: NobodyKnows]
[ar: Boyzone]
[ti: Nobody Knows]
[al: BZ20 (Deluxe Edition)]
[by:Dirk L. Nicolaas]
[00:01.85]Nobody Knows - Boyzone
[00:06.83]I pretend that I'm glad you went away
[00:10.27]
[00:12.42]These four walls closing more every day
[00:15.81]
[00:16.53]Now I'm dying inside
[00:18.76]
[00:20.08]Nobody knows it but me
[00:23.30]
[00:29.17]Like a clown, I put on a show
[00:32.52]
[00:34.63]The pain is real even if nobody knows
[00:38.31]
[00:38.88]That I'm crying inside
[00:41.24]
[00:42.16]And nobody knows it but me
[00:45.73]
[00:50.43]Why didn't I say
[00:52.06]
[00:52.99]The things I needed to say
[00:55.10]
[00:55.97]How could I let my angel get away
[01:00.53]
[01:01.19]Now my world is just
[01:03.34]
[01:04.73]Tumbling let down
[01:06.20]
[01:07.84]I can see it so clearly
[01:09.72]
[01:10.46]But you don't know we're around
[01:12.80]
[01:13.77]Nights are lonely, days so sad
[01:17.41]
[01:19.25]And I just keep thinking about the love that we had
[01:22.94]
[01:23.54]Now I'm missing you
[01:25.61]
[01:26.97]Nobody knows it but me
[01:29.80]
[01:36.14]I carry a smile when I'm broken in two
[01:39.66]
[01:40.62]And I'm nobody without someone like you
[01:45.17]
[01:46.22]I'm trembling inside
[01:48.48]
[01:49.14]And nobody knows it but me
[01:52.41]
[01:58.55]I lie awake, it's a quarter past three
[02:01.91]
[02:02.98]I'm screaming at night if I thought you would hear me
[02:07.84]
[02:08.60]My heart is calling you
[02:10.63]
[02:11.44]And nobody knows it but me
[02:14.62]
[02:19.80]How broken I get
[02:22.17]You could ask my heart
[02:24.46]
[02:25.01]But like a jigsaw puzzle it's been torn all apart
[02:29.92]
[02:30.57]A billion words couldn't say
[02:32.78]
[02:33.68]Just how I feel
[02:35.77]A million years from now you'll know it
[02:39.26]I'll be loving you still
[02:41.96]
[02:43.05]Nights are lonely, days so sad
[02:46.71]
[02:47.32]And I just keep thinking about the love that we had
[02:52.25]
[02:52.80]Now I'm missing you
[02:54.82]
[02:56.19]Nobody knows it but me
[02:59.52]
[03:11.21]Nobody knows it
[03:12.98]No, nobody knows it
[03:14.98]
[03:21.80]Nobody, nobody
[03:23.21]
[03:25.67]Sitting and the nights are lonely
[03:28.27]Nights are lonely, days so sad
[03:31.34]
[03:33.50]I just keep thinking about the love that we had
[03:36.89]
[03:37.49]Now I'm missing you
[03:39.21]
[03:41.05]Nobody knows it but me
[03:44.13]Nobody knows it
[03:45.77]
[03:46.32]No, nobody but me
[03:49.21]
[03:50.14]Nights are lonely, days so sad
[03:53.70]
[03:55.94]I just keep thinking about the love that we had
[03:59.18]
[03:59.98]Now I'm missing you
[04:01.96]
[04:03.37]Nobody knows it but me
[999:00.00]***Terima kasih***
